[{"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " listen, do you guys think i have a chance with janine?", "answer": " honey, we have been through this before!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " yeah. don&#146;t do this to yourself.", "answer": " she&#146;s made it pretty clear, it is not going to happen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " well all right then, i guess i shouldn&#146;t get to excited about the fact  that i just kissed her!", "answer": " you serious?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " that&#146;s great!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " yeah well, we&#146;ll see.", "answer": " you kissed her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh we kissed it up real nice.", "answer": " so you kissed her, so what happened after that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i came over here to tell you guys.", "answer": " so she&#146;s just waiting over there for ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i gotta go.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna be really late for dance class!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " have you kissed her yet? it&#146;s awesome! i could do it forever! y&#146;know what? she-she kisses better than my mom cooks!", "answer": " i am so glad you said cooks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i know.", "answer": "  oh hey rachel, sweetheart? you have got to tell the post office that you have moved. okay? we are still getting all your bills and stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh-oh, pottery barn!  you can throw the rest away.", "answer": " i&#146;m not your garbage man. i&#146;m your mailman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " you got it from pottery barn?!", "answer": " yeah! it&#146;s an apothecary table. does anyone even know what an apothecary is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " rach, phoebe hates pottery barn.", "answer": " i hate pottery barn too. they kicked me out of there just because i sat on a bed!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " you took off your pants and climbed under the sheets!", "answer": "  i was tired!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " phoebe hates pottery barn?!", "answer": " yeah, she hates all mass produced stuff. she thinks her furniture should have a history, a story behind it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well this has story behind it! i mean they had to ship it all the way from the white plains store.", "answer": " it&#146;s gotta be one of a kind. y&#146;know like umm, y&#146;know uh, what&#146;s that god awful ceramic fruit bowl she has on her counter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " hey! i made that for her!", "answer": " you made pottery?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " yeah! i made it of this fruit bowl i found in the garbage.", "answer": " i&#146;m telling&#151;if you put that in her apartment you&#146;ll never hear the end of it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " okay fine! i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll just tell her it&#146;s an antique apothecary table, she doesn&#146;t have to know where it came from. oh! look at this little drawers! oh look-look it says that it holds 300 cds.", "answer": " ahh, just like the apothecary tables of yore&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " i am so glad you guys got together, chandler and i are always looking for a couple to go out with and now we have one!", "answer": " look at us, we&#146;re a couple of couples!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i had so much fun tonight, and what a great restaurant.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " and chandler i can&#146;t believe i let you pay for this one.  thanks man.", "answer": " so do you guys gonna come over tomorrow? i&#146;ll make that pasta thing i was telling you about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh that would be great!", "answer": " oh, but hey look, at least let us bring the wine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " joey, you don&#146;t have too!", "answer": " nope-op! i insist!  you get the wine right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah all right.  okay, good night guys.", "answer": " see ya tomorrow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " tomorrow!", "answer": " can&#146;t wait!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " how are we gonna get out of that one?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " i can&#146;t handle two nights in a row with them.", "answer": " what-what&#146;s wrong with monica and chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know, they&#146;re just a little blah!", "answer": " blah?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " well y&#146;know, he&#146;s blah, she&#146;s just&#151;she&#146;s very loud for such a small person.", "answer": " uh, they&#146;re like my best friends. are you saying we can&#146;t hang out with them? &#145;cause that would kinda be a problem.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " no! of course we can still hang out with them. just y&#146;know, not two nights in a row. okay?", "answer": " i guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  ooh, what a great table! where-where did you get it?", "answer": " guess!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " umm, a flea market?", "answer": " ha! see, i knew, i knew you&#146;d get it on the first guess. isn&#146;t it cool! it&#146;s an apothecary table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " wow! oh you can just imagine that this is where  they kept all the stuff to make their potions.", "answer": " ohh, yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " y&#146;know? ooh, you can almost smell the opium.", "answer": " almost.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " how much was it?", "answer": " it was only 500 bucks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " 500 bucks at a flea market?!", "answer": " oh, okay see i thought, i thought you meant how much was it when it was new, y&#146;know like back then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh no.", "answer": " yeah no, i mean it was at a flea market, so it was y&#146;know, it was like a dollar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " a dollar?", "answer": " and fifty. so it was like one and fifty dollars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " ohh, okay, they gave you the old time pricing.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " well, what period is it from?", "answer": " uh, it&#146;s from yore. like the days of yore. y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " yes, yes i do. god, oh it&#146;s just perfect! wow! i bet it has a great story behind it too. did they tell you anything? like y&#146;know where it was from or&#133;", "answer": " yes! that i know, this is from white plains.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey! we&#146;re here!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  ohh! oh my god!", "answer": " you like it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh no!", "answer": " it&#146;s my new apothecary table!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " ross! phoebe&#146;s gonna be here any second, she cannot see this!", "answer": " well why not?! she&#146;ll-she&#146;ll love it! it&#146;s the real thing! i got it at pottery barn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i know you did! i bought the same one! and if she sees your table she&#146;s gonna know that i lied to her. i told her ours was an original.", "answer": " why did you do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " because she hates pottery barn.", "answer": " she hates pottery barn?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i know! i know, she says it&#146;s all mass-produced, nothing is authentic, and everyone winds up having the same stuff.  so come on, she&#146;s gonna be here any second! can we please just cover this up with something?! please?", "answer": " what? no! no! i am not gonna hide it from phoebe&#151;ooh, although i did get some great pottery barn sheets!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " ooo! oh, i forgot they made sheets!", "answer": " uh, yeah! i still can&#146;t believe she hates pottery barn!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " ross, get over it! it&#146;s not like she hates you.", "answer": " yeah but pottery barn! y&#146;know what i think? it&#146;s just she-she&#146;s weird. y&#146;know it&#146;s because she&#146;s a twin. twins are weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " ross, she&#146;s not weird, she just wants her stuff to be one of a kind.", "answer": " huh. y&#146;know what&#146;s not one of a kind? a twin!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " ooh, phoebe&#146;s here! okay, let&#146;s turn out all the lights and we&#146;ll just watch the movie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh, you like it? you wanna know where i got it?", "answer": " sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " he got it a flea market!", "answer": " you bought your sheets at a flea market? ross come on, you gotta loosen the purse strings a little.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " the dinner will be ready in twenty minutes. this is so exciting.", "answer": " and here is the bottle of wine for you to bring over tonight.  you were also going to buy monica flowers but you couldn&#146;t afford it, because you paid dinner last night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " thanks. thanks, but uh actually it&#146;s just gonna be me again tonight.", "answer": " what happened to janine?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh, she&#146;s uh-uh really sick.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s too bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yeah, she&#146;s been in there all day , uh high fever, a nose problem&#133; phlegm! phlegm! phlegm-phlegm-phlegm!", "answer": "  monica! chandler! i&#146;m really-really sorry about tonight. i don&#146;t know if joey told you; i just couldn&#146;t get out of going to this play. i&#146;m sorry. have a great time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " &#145;kay!", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no-no, she really is sick!", "answer": " then why-why is she going to a play?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " uh, y&#146;know, starve a fever, go to a play for a cold.", "answer": " joey! why is janine not coming over for dinner?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well uh, she didn&#146;t want to hang out with you guys two nights in a row. i&#146;m so sorry.", "answer": " well, why does she not want to hang out with us?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " because she uh, she-she thinks that you are blah and that you, monica, are too loud.", "answer": "  what?!!  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " so she was just pretending to have a good time last night? she was lying to our faces?!", "answer": " ugh, i can not believe this! i mean, who is she to judge us? we could not have been nicer to her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " and i am not blah, i am a hoot!", "answer": " i know! i know! come on, please-please you guys, don&#146;t-don&#146;t be mad. i&#146;m sure she just, she just said that stuff because she was nervous and you guys are like my best friends! y&#146;know? and it was our first date! plus, she&#146;s really sick!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " no, you sh&#151;no you said you made that up!!", "answer": " i know, but don&#146;t you think the sick thing is way better than the play thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " come on you guys, come on please-please just give her another chance, huh? she&#146;ll come around i promise.", "answer": " of course we will, come on we gotta make dinner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  i do not like that woman!", "answer": "  i can hear you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey pheebs, could you please not put your feet up on my new&#133;&#133;old sheet?", "answer": " oh sure!  noo!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " ohh!!", "answer": " my apothecary table!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " noooooo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " ross, where did you get this?!", "answer": " i got it at pottery barn!! okay?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " oh my god, phoebe, pottery barn has ripped off the design of our antique!", "answer": " wow! oh my god, well if they&#146;ve ripped off our table ours must be much more than one and fifty dollars!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh yes.", "answer": " well this doesn&#146;t even smell like opium.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " of course not, it smells like wine, which you spilled! and thanks for wrecking my sheet by the way.", "answer": " oh ross, calm down, i&#146;ll give you the 80 cents.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " okay, one more time.", "answer": " chandler, would you like some more orange juice?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " perfect decibel.", "answer": "  i know!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " so uh, what are you guys doing?", "answer": " oh nothing, we&#146;re just talking. y&#146;know, blah-blah-blah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " look, come on you guys, you said you were gonna try! all right look, i came over here to invite you guys to a movie with me and janine.", "answer": " well, i&#146;d like to but,  i&#146;m not sure we have time to go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " ha-ha, very funny&#151;look! i don&#146;t know what to do! i really want you guys to get along. just please come to the movie with us. i mean you owe me!", "answer": " we owe you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " that&#146;s right! i helped you guys out a lot in the start of your relationship. huh? i helped you guys sneak around for like six months, and i looked like an idiot! and i was humiliated. and i only made 200 dollars!", "answer": " we didn&#146;t give you any money!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " &#133;see i can&#146;t decide whether it would go better next to the new wicker dining chair, the sahara desk, or the parker console table.", "answer": " wow! i didn&#146;t know that there was a pottery barn up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " i know, i know. i went a little crazy.", "answer": " a little? your place looks like page 72 of the catalogue. oh look at that! the ornamental bird cage! large!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  oh ross no. be careful, that is very old! okay? early colonial bird merchants used to bring their birds to market in that.", "answer": "  fascinating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": "  another amazing find! wow! oh i bet this has a great story too!", "answer": " oh it does, it does! it is a room separating apparatus from colonial times.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " ah!", "answer": " hmm, a lot of this stuff is from colonial times. hey, what are some other time periods rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " well there&#146;s yore. and uh, y&#146;know, yesteryear.", "answer": " yeah no, i&#146;m telling you rachel has such a great eye for this stuff. ross, y&#146;know if you ever decide you need to redecorate&#151;and i think that you should. you should, you should ask rachel to help.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh honey he doesn&#146;t need my help.", "answer": " oh, come on! i think he&#146;s ready to get rid of, what did you call it? the cheap knock-offs and dinosaur junk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " really?!  hey, y&#146;know what? since you have such a great sense of what i need, uh ooh, here&#146;s-here&#146;s 60 bucks, why don&#146;t you take phoebe down to that colonial flea market of yours and get me some stuff.", "answer": "  y&#146;know what? i don&#146;t, i don&#146;t think phoebe really wants to come.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " no! i do want to!", "answer": " oh, she does want to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " she does want to.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " pheebs, i don&#146;t know what to say. i guess the flea market was just better last time.", "answer": " well at least i got these sheets for ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " uck, look at this! pottery barn, yuck!", "answer": " yeah, y&#146;know what? don&#146;t look at it.  seriously, don&#146;t look at it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " no! look-look! there&#146;s the coffee table they stole from us!", "answer": " ugh, those bastards! let&#146;s go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " that fan kinda looks like ours. and the birdcage and the&#133;wait a sec! this is our exact living room!", "answer": " no! no! no! no it&#146;s not! no it&#146;s not! come on! phoebe, ours is totally different! i mean we don&#146;t have the&#133;  we don&#146;t have the&#133;that lamp! and-and that screen is y&#146;know, on the other side.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh my god. this is where you got all our stuff, pottery barn! oh my god!", "answer": " okay! okay-okay look&#151;no i did, i just wanted this stuff and i know how you feel about pottery barn. just&#133; come on don&#146;t be mad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " no-no-no, but i am mad! i am mad! because this stuff is everything that is wrong with the world! and it&#146;s all sitting up in my living room and all i can think about is how i don&#146;t have that lamp!", "answer": " well then honey, buy the lamp! hey, we have that 60 bucks from ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " i can&#146;t! i can&#146;t! unless&#133; well are you saying that-that you would move out if-if i didn&#146;t buy that lamp?", "answer": " what?! no! i&#146;m not gonna move out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " but are you saying that you would move out if i didn&#146;t buy that lamp?", "answer": "  oh. yes! i would so move out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay then i don&#146;t have a choice! i have to buy that lamp!", "answer": " that&#146;s right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " well, this-this-this was great. didn&#146;t everybody have a great time?", "answer": " well i did. i really did. and you guys, i&#146;ve got to say, i&#146;m sorry if i was a little weird after the last time we went out. i guess i was just nervous or something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " that&#146;s totally understandable.", "answer": " don&#146;t worry about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " so we can go out again?", "answer": " oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " absolutely!", "answer": " oh good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh well then, good night!", "answer": " good night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " see? eh, wasn&#146;t that fun?", "answer": " we have got to move!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  i knew it!! y&#146;know, you&#146;re not so quiet yourself, missy!", "answer": " and i&#146;m blah? listen, the only thing more boring than watching modern dance is having to listen to you talk about it,  &quot;oh chandler, i just lost myself in the moment.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " y&#146;know, i know you&#146;re talking, but all i hear is, &quot;blah. blah. blah-blah-blah.&quot;", "answer": "  all right! you and me! let&#146;s go! right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": "  y&#146;know i think you can take her.", "answer": "  you&#146;d better hope i don&#146;t see you in the hallway!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " all right, uh, we&#146;ve got a little bit of a problem here. these people are my friends; you can&#146;t treat them that way.", "answer": " they said stuff to me too, y&#146;know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i know! i know! and i&#146;m going to talk to them about it. they mean so much to me. they&#133; they&#146;re like my family. if you guys are gonna be fighting all the time, i-i&#133; i don&#146;t think we can be together. it just, it just can&#146;t work. it can&#146;t.  i&#146;m very upset.", "answer": " okay. okay. would, would it help if i went over and apologized?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " what did i tell you about the hall?!", "answer": " i was just coming over here to apologize for my behavior! i&#146;d really like it if we could be friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " well, i know that would make joey happy, so, i would like that too.", "answer": " great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " now come on.  well, i&#146;m glad we worked things out.", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i&#146;ll see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": "  or i&#146;ll hear you.", "answer": "  that&#146;s it big girl!  come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " did you hear that?", "answer": " yeah uh, what am i gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;m sorry man.  you wanna go watch?", "answer": " yeah!  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " how ya doin&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " hey so, did uh, did she move out?", "answer": " pretty much, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " i cannot believe you broke up with her just like that.", "answer": " well, when it&#146;s not right, you know it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " you okay?", "answer": " yeah! yeah. i&#146;ll be all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " y&#146;know what would cheer you up?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " i&#146;m giving this lecture on erosion theories tomorrow night, i think you should come.", "answer": "  you&#146;re right! that did cheer me up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}]